威尔 · 森特斯: 伊森会的，因为它会传到更远的地方给伊森。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Ethan's gonna because
it's gonna down further over to Ethan.
Ethan: 所以用户函数存储一个对象，但是
&gt;&gt; Ethan: So
user function stores an object but
它可以包含除了函数以外的任何东西，对吗？
it can contain anything other
than functions to right?
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，当然，当然。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
absolutely, absolutely.
伊森: 你也会用同样的方式引用它。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: And
you'd reference it the same way.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，是的，顺便说一下，我们一会儿见
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, yeah,
it also by the way, we'll see you later
可能还有一个隐藏的原型财产。
on may also have a hidden
proto property on it as well.
我的天啊，是后来的伊森，继续。
My goodness,
it was the later on Ethan go ahead.
伊森: 所以 object.create 接受的论点是,
&gt;&gt; Ethan: So the argument that
object.create accepts is that the,
一直都是原型吗？
that is always the Proto?
威尔 · 森塔斯: 首先，在原始文学中，人们总是认为。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Well first that
is always thought in the Proto.
说得好，谢谢。
Yeah, very well put, thank you.
你想继续调查吗？
You want to follow up on that?
伊森: 没有，只是澄清一下。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: No, just clarifying.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，这是一个很好的澄清问题。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
that's a great clarification question.
换句话说。
Putting it another way.
伊森: 我现在不是在引用 MDN，而是在问你。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Instead of referencing MDN
at this moment, I'm just ask you.
[ LAUGH }威尔 · 森塔斯: 这是事实,
[LAUGH}
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's a true fact,
create 创建一个带有隐藏 proto 属性的空对象。
object.create creates an empty
object with a hidden proto property.
现在，我要说的是，这个属性不像我们的词法范围属性那样隐藏。
Now, I will say this, that property is not
as hidden as our Lexical scope property.
那个你看不到，或者是我们自己的实现数组。
That one you can't see, or
our own fulfilled array.
由于某种原因，没有任何控制台显示这一点。
No console shows that for some reason.
这个隐藏属性如果你在 Chrome Dev 工具中控制台日志用户1,
This hidden property if you in the Chrome
Dev tools were to console log user1,
你会在 Chrome 开发工具控制台上看到一个小小的向下箭头。
you'd see the little down arrow
in the Chrome Dev tools console.
如果你点击它，你会看到这个原型属性和
If you click that,
you'd see this proto property and
用户功能存储的链接。
a link to user function store.
所以这是一个隐藏的，但你可以看到它。
So this is one that's hidden but
you can see it.
是的，继续，继续。
Yeah, more, go ahead.
伊森: 所以技术上来说，这是不赞成的，但是你可以使用。 我认为 getPrototype,
&gt;&gt; Ethan: So technically it's deprecated
but you can use .getPrototype of I think,
这是一种新的办法，实际上得到它正式。
which is a new method of
actually getting it officially.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 太好了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Excellent.
伊森: 但是浏览器的书呆子们可能是因为它是原始的
&gt;&gt; Ethan: But the browser wonks
probably move __proto because it's
有点像内置的永久。
kinda built-in forever.
Will Sentance: 太好了，我们保持了 JavaScript 历史的一致性。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Perfect, we maintain the
consistency of the history of JavaScript.
非常好，一直都在工作。
Excellent, always working with it.
好了，各位，我们现在,
All right, people, so let's now,
是啊，我们现在就去吧
yeah, let's now actually go ahead and
运行增量方法。
run that increment method.
这是我的执行环境，我已经准备好了。
There's my execution context,
I'm ready to go.
让我们一如既往地说清楚,
Let' just be really clear, as always,
这个执行上下文消失了，从代码中弹出。
this execution context is gone,
popped off the code side.
让我们进入并运行 increment。
Let's go in and run increment.
本地内存是常见的。
Local memory is usual.
我们就把它放在那儿吧。
Let's just put it there.
我想问一些事情，增量代码，我们可以看到我
I want to ask something,
increments code we can see I
把它放在一行里但是 Braden 它的代码是什么？
put it in one line there, but,
Braden, what is its code?
只要给我准确的话，我有时候会要求的话
Just give me the exact words,
what I've sometimes asked for
用精确的词语来描述，对吗？
to relate in the exact words, right?
它的代码是什么？
What is its code?
布雷登: This.score + + 。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: This.score ++.
威尔 · 森特斯: This.scorel + 。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: This.scorel++.
问题是，这个递增函数不需要在用户1上运行,
Here's the problem, this increment
function doesn't need to work on user 1,
不需要在用户2上工作，不需要在用户403上工作。
doesn't need to work on user 2,
doesn't need to work on user 403.
没错。
Yeah, exactly.
所有人。
All of them.
所以这个增量方法。
So this increment method.
我想如果我想在 user1上工作，在 user1里面,
I guess if I wanted to work on user1,
inside of it,
我需要写 user1.score + + 。
I'm going to need to write user1.score ++.
这样他们就可以去找我们，找到学校的财产并实施它。
So that they can go and look for us one
find the school property and implement it.
但是问题是当时运行 user2.increment 和
But then the problem is by then
run it user2.increment and
1.score + + .
inside running inside of
increment ran user1.score++.
所以我需要这个方法使这个函数在 user1或 user1上工作
So I need this method this
function to be working on user1 or
User2or user4 or user405.
user2or user4 or user405.
不要惊慌，我有一个惊人的东西。
Don't panic, I have an amazing thing.
我在当地的记忆中太渺小了。
I'm in my local memory too small with me.
我有一个神奇的东西叫做隐含参数。
I've an amazing thing called
an implicit parameter.
这意味着一个，我甚至没有指定。
That means one, I don't even specify.
这是一个自动存在并自动填补我的空白。
It's one that's automatically there and
automatically filled in for me.
它叫做这个。
And it's called this.
一旦我开始在本地内存中运行这个方法,
As soon as I start running this
method increment in my local memory,
你知道我得到了什么吗？
you know what I get?
不需要自动解析视图,
Without parsing the view
just automatically,
我得到一个隐式参数占位符。
I get an implicit parameter placeholder.
隐含的意思是我没有写它，它在那里等着我，这个，还有
Implicit meaning I didn't write it,
it's there for me, this and
你觉得它会自动分配给它什么呢 Todd？
what do you think it's gonna have
automatically assigned to it Todd?
用户1。
&gt;&gt; Todd: User1.
威尔 · 森特斯: 用户1，不管那个点左边是什么,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: User1, whatever is
to the left hand side of that dot,
重要的是在那个物体上运行。
that matters being run on that,
on that object.
不管左边是什么对象，都会有 User1。
Whatever object's on left hand side,
there will be User1.
事实上所有函数和全局自动然而这个但是
In fact all functions and
global automatically however this but
除了我们今天要看的其他几个有趣的案子
besides a couple of other interesting
cases we're going to see today
总是有人在谈论这件事。
that this is always there
is a talk about it.
在用户创建中我们有这个，但是
In user creates we had of this, but
它指的是一些不太有用的东西。
it referred to something
that was not too useful.
这是 JavaScript 窗口中一个有趣的全局对象概念
This is a funny global object
concept in JavaScript window or
全局对象，你可能见过一两次。
global object you may have seen it once or
twice.
所以如果我们试着在用户创建者内部使用它,
And so if we were to try and
use this, inside a user creator,
我们会指向一些有趣的全局对象。
we'd be pointing off some
funny global object thing.
某种随机的小东西。
Some sort of random little object thing.
它没有多少用处，但是当它是一个函数增量时,
It wouldn't have not much use, but
when instead it's a function increment,
因此调用用户1或用户2对象。
thus being called upon the user 1 or
the user 2 object.
但是因此需要对每个对象都是通用的，可重用的。
But therefore needs to be general,
reusable on each of these objects.
谢天谢地，我们有了这个隐含的参数。
Thank goodness we have
this implicit parameter.
这个小小的占位器，这是我们的一个关键规则，它总是连着它自己
This little place holder, here's our one
key rule, it always attaches to itself
对象的左手边的点，这个函数正在运行。
the object to the left hand side of the
dots on which that function is being run.
那么这个. score + Todd，计算变成了什么？
So what does this .score++ Todd,
evaluate to turn into?
1.score + + .
&gt;&gt; Todd: User1.score++.
威尔 · 森特斯: 干得好，托德。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Very nice one, Todd.
1.score + + .
Use1.score++.
用户1不在本地内存中，我们前往全局，它在那里。
User 1 not in local memory,
we head out to global, there it is.
得分，增加到4。
Score, increment it to 4.
漂亮，是的。
Beautiful, yeah.
老乡们，我们将会看到这个的另一个主要用途。
Folk, we're gonna see
another major use of this.
关键词，又来了，每次都有一个主要用户在一瞬间。
Keyword, there we go,
every time another major user in a moment.
但是现在这是我们的关键用途，运行一个共享或者
But for now this is our key use,
run a function that shared or
可以通过原始链接对许多不同的对象使用。
going to be available to many different
objects through the proto link.
并且确保我们用关键字 this 来写它，以访问对象
And make sure we write it with the keyword
this to access the object on which that
方法，那个函数被执行到点的右边。
method, that function is being executed
to the right-hand side of the dot.
对这些人竖起大拇指。
Thumbs on this people.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，杰森。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, Jason.
我们去找马克。
We'll go to Mark.
先是杰森，然后是马克。
Jason first, then Mark.
说吧，杰森。
Go ahead, Jason.
杰森: 当这个操作符运行时，我们是否显式地使用名称空间,
&gt;&gt; Jason: Are we explicitly working with
namespaces when this operator is in play,
因为要找到我们的价值，就必须去寻找范围的要求。
because of the scoping requirements where
it has to go look to find our value.
威尔 · 森特斯: 我们都完全知道这里面是什么
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We all absolutely
knowing that the this inside of here is
只有在这个执行上下文中。
related to,
it is only within this execution context.
不过，这是从哪里来的呢？
Where is the this coming from though?
我们马上就会看到，我们可以用一些有趣的方式来玩它。
We'll see in just a moment that we can
play with it in some interesting ways.
马克，我们一会儿就知道了？
We'll see in a moment, Mark?
这是本地执行上下文吗？
&gt;&gt; Mark: Is this local execution context?
我们正在明确地讨论这个问题。
We're explicitly talking about this.
但它正在访问全局内存中的分数，或者
But it's accessing score
up in global memory, or
不用返回值就可以改变它，这是我们传统的做法。
changing it without say a return value,
which we've done traditionally.
威尔 · 森特斯: 当然，所以你是说这可能像一个,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Sure, so
you're saying this might be like a,
你对这种副作用很谨慎。
you're cautious about this as
a sort of side effect type thing.
是的，绝对的，绝对的，这就是为什么，但是
Yeah, absolutely, absolutely,
and that's why, but
这是这个型号的标准配置。
it's totally standard within this model.
这并不是天生的问题。
And it's not inherently problematic.
但这就是为什么我们必须接受如果我们采用这种模式,
But it is why we have to accept that,
if we're taking this model,
如果我们要组织代码，就要权衡利弊。
if we're organizing our code,
there's trade-offs.
巨大的好处，我的数据或我的功能或
Huge benefit, my data or
my functionality or
这个功能捆绑在一个地方的可用性。
the availability of that
functionality bundled in one place.
问题是，在功能方面，它可能在我的代码中的任何地方产生影响
Problem, around the functionality, it can
have consequences anywhere in my code
但是，理想情况下，只有在我试图瞄准的目标物体内部。
base, ideally, though, only within
the object I'm trying to target.
但是，维护这种代码库肯定会有起伏。
But maintaining this sort of code base
can be definitely have its ups and downs.
马克问得很好。
Very fair question from Mark.